It's time to see where you can take a trade
and we will start the trade
[Music]
In Chowka Trade Chowk, we will
understand from both Santosh and Gaurav where their focus is
and Santosh, you are very welcome,
festive greetings to you too, tell me which
stocks are on your radar,
yes, good afternoon everyone and best
wishes to everyone for the festival season. So today there
is definitely a lot of pressure in the broader market and in the broader market, where the
leadership came from the PSU sector, today there is
major profit booking.
My first call is on the self side of HAL.
Here a breakdown of a classical head and shoulder
formation is visible.
Clearly negative divergence is also visible in the RSI, so it is
possible that some pressure may be seen building in the stock. There will be a
stop loss of ₹1000000. On the buying side, I have a
slightly defensive bet. Rabo Children is
outperforming even in today's weak market.
Today, some buying is being seen in some hospital stocks.
This stock is
in a very strong uptrend after a consolidation.  The
stock is giving a breakout of the symmetric triangle formation. The stock is trading above its 20 day
low.
Buy here. Your target will be here
in Rainbow Children. Your target will be 00 and the
stop loss will be 1090.
Tosh ji's opinion is to buy Rainbow Children
and along with this, the sell opinion is on HAL
where you have been given a target till 1800.
Let's move ahead. Gaurav, I turn to you.
Tell me where are your eyes? I will have a buy and sell
recommendation.
If we talk about buying, it will be
in ICICI General Insurance. If you
look at it, we have seen a breakout of a falling channel.
Today, follow-through buying is coming and is
sustaining. A few days ago, a
bullish crossover also came a day or two ago. So, it
seems that you may see a follow-through buying here. The
target in this will be 1450. The
stop loss will be 1370. The second one is
Indian Hotels, where there will be a sell recommendation. It is
quite strong and quite big here.
A bearish pattern has formed, it has
given a breakdown of a rising wedge and a swing
low has formed, so in the lower time frames it has already
come into a downtrend, the breakdown has
also happened in it, so here I
feel that you can see good pressure which is mounted in it,
so
here you can sell Indian Tel for 380, it has
come down a bit, so the
revised stop loss will be of 410,
okay, so there is a sell opinion in Indian Hotels
and along with this you are also
getting a buy call in III Lord.